"This episode contains explicit content that
may be inappropriate for younger viewers."
Who is this frail but beautiful woman in
the plaza of the Clock Village of Rostolf,
out of money and hungry,
who looks like she's about to cry?
That's right, it's me.
Sadly, it is me.
"A Deep Sorrow from the Past"
I need to make money somehow, huh?
Hm?
"Recruiting witch for ultra-short-term work.
It's a chance to make a lot of money."
"If you are interested, please come
to the following address immediately."
This is...
Let's see... it's from...
The Lavender Witch, Estelle?
So, Elaina, since you've come to see me,
I can assume that you're willing to work, right?
I do want to make money.
Are you willing to work?
If possible, I'd like to make
money without working.
Oh, well. Even if you're not
motivated to work, a witch is a witch.
So, you seem pretty young. How old are you?
I'll be 18 this year.
When did you become a witch?
When I was 14.
Oh, it was a year later than me.
How old were you when you
became an apprentice witch?
When I was ten, I think?
So you're saying it took you
three years to become a witch?
I became a witch after one year.
It took you two years longer, huh?
How old are you right now?
Nineteen...
Oh, you're a year older than me.
Are you making fun of me?
No, no, of course not.
So, what's the payment for the job?
You're more interested in the money
than what the job actually is, huh?
Then, let's talk about the payment first.
That's contingent upon success.
Once my job is completed,
I'll give you all of it.
Are you serious?
I'm very serious.
But, what kind of job do I need
to do to receive so much money?
Hm? Don't tell me you're getting nervous?
Don't worry.
I just want you to accompany me.
Accompany you? Where?
Before I tell you, do you know
about the 2nd District Murderer?
Second District Murderer?
It sounds like a troubling matter.
It's a famous story that
everyone in this country knows.
Huh?
It's a true story that
even has a play and a book.
Ten years ago...
A robber went into the house of
a wealthy family in the 2nd District.
The wealthy couple inside the house were killed,
but Selena, their only daughter,
was out shopping and was safe.
The one bright spot of this tragedy, huh?
It wasn't, though.
Selena was taken in by her uncle,
but she suffered horrible abuse,
and darkness grew in her heart,
making her hate people and the wretched world.
Selena stabbed her uncle to death,
stabbing him over and over.
And then she disappeared.
Don't tell me, the girl, Selena--
Yeah. She's the 2nd District Murderer.
She...
...was my childhood friend.
We were really close, like real sisters...
But I ended up going abroad to study magic.
And when I came back from
my studies, Selena was already...
After discovering the pleasure of killing,
she continued on her spree,
killing people one after another...
Three years ago, she was
finally caught and executed.
I caught her.
And I executed her.
With these hands, I cut off her head.
I really wanted to save her...
I wanted to give her a chance
to atone for what she did...
But as someone working for the country,
the king's order was absolute.
Ahem.
So then, Estelle,
what does that story have to do with
where you'd like me to accompany you?
I want to save that girl.
That's why I want you to come with me.
Save?
You said she was executed
three years ago, right?
That's right.
That's why we need to go...
...to ten years ago.
How do you plan on going back to ten years ago?
Ever since the day I executed Selena,
I've been researching magic to go back in time.
In order to avoid that unhappy ending.
That girl was in this country ten years ago.
That girl, back when she was
still a decent human being.
I want to prevent the robber
from killing Selena's parents.
If I do that, I'm sure
Selena's future will be saved.
I want to do things over.
I don't want to live in a world
without her in it anymore...
I understand the situation now,
but I don't understand
how you're planning to do it.
Even if you are to go back in time,
why do you need my power?
Follow me.
The magic I created to go
back in time is not simple.
It wasn't something I could make
without sacrificing anything.
Which means?
When they don't have enough magic,
mages can sacrifice something of
themselves to create more magic, right?
Yes. I suppose that's true.
Like their voice or memories.
What did you sacrifice in
order to complete your magic?
Blood.
I've been letting out as much
of my blood as I could and storing it,
and outside of that,
I've been storing magic, as well.
In order to travel back in time ten years,
you need an astounding amount of magic.
But, it's still not enough.
I just need a little more.
How much do you need?
If I pour out all the magic
inside me, I'll have just enough.
In other words, once you travel back
in time, you won't have any magic left,
so you're bringing another witch along
to protect you in case anything happens?
Not quite.
What's that?
If we put these rings on,
then we can share our magic.
Share our magic...?
If I put this on, then
even if you have no magic,
you can use my power to do magic?
That's right.
What do you think?
Will you do it?
I'm a traveler...
...so I'm a little interested to see what
this country was like ten years ago.
Are you ready?
Then, I'm going to do it.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm just anemic.
You're sweating, too, though.
That's because I'm anemic, too.
You don't seem fine...
But I'm still going to do it.
If I don't do it when I can,
then I'll lose my chance.
That's true.
I'll ask again.
Are you ready?
Are you ready, Estelle?
I'm totally ready.
I've been ready for years!
Oh, sorry!
I forgot to tell you something!
What is it?
Thanks!
You're welcome.
It looks like it worked.
The date is from ten years ago...
It's hard to believe,
but it looks like it did work.
Let's hurry.
Our time limit is one hour.
When the clock strikes six,
we'll be brought back to our own time.
We only have one hour?
That was all I could manage with my magic.
But,
it's enough.
If we've got that much time,
it'll be easy to make it so the
next ten years never happened.
What's the plan?
In about twenty minutes,
a robber wearing a black hood
will break into Selena's house,
and stab her parents repeatedly.
So we'll get her parents
out before that happens,
ambush the robber, and drive the robber away.
Easy, right?
I hope everything goes according to plan.
I'll make sure it does.
If her parents live,
then I'm sure Selena's life
would not take the turn it did.
If that's the case,
then the ten-years-later Rostolf
we return to will be very different.
That won't happen.
Just because we meddled in the past
won't change the fact that
I killed Selena in the future.
In other words,
the world we will return to is
the world that was already there,
but the world without the murderer
will exist on a completely different time axis.
Um, I don't mean to be rude,
but is there any point in that?
That really is rude.
In our world, Selena will
still have been executed.
There is a point.
By doing this, it makes me feel better.
Just thinking that there's a future
where she was saved is enough.
Is that how it works?
It is.
Huh? Hey, w-wait!
Selena!
H-Huh? Miss? Who are you?
I'm sorry! I couldn't save you this whole time.
I'm so, so sorry!
Um, Miss, who are you?
I'll definitely, definitely save you!
Is this, like, a new way of proselytizing?
Oh, I was acting suspicious, huh?
Sorry.
You still are, in a present progressive sense.
I really am sorry.
I just wanted to hug you.
Are you, like, a new kind
of pervert or something?
I came here from the future.
I'm in the middle of my shopping, so I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
Right, sorry.
Wait for me, Selena.
It looks like you were treated very coldly...
She's always been like that.
But you know, even though she talks like that,
inside, she's really kind.
I know.
Let's go.
It's time to get started.
You're Estelle's older half-sister?
I didn't know she had a half sister.
But you do look a lot like her.
That's true. The nape and line of
your neck are the same as Estelle's.
What's going on?
Don't worry about that.
Is it really okay not to?
It's fine.
Anyway, this is a message from my father.
He wants to talk to you about something
important that happened to Estelle
during her study abroad, so he asks
that you please come with me immediately.
I have no idea what's going on...
But, well, why not?
Thank you. This way please.
It really worked.
Estelle just needs to come back and
then all that's left is to wait for the robber.
In a few minutes,
a black-hooded robber will appear.
Isn't it taking a long time?
For Estelle and the robber...
...and stab her parents repeatedly.
Stab repeatedly, huh...?
Would someone really go that far in a robbery?
Could it have been a crime
committed because of a grudge
that was made to look like a robbery?
My magic's being sucked out of the ring...
Which means, Estelle is fighting someone...
Her opponent is probably the robber.
But a blade can't beat an
opponent who can use magic.
It's a pain, so I hope everything's
settled by the time I get there.
Is it over...?
That's right...
We... Estelle, and I...
Everything we imagined...
everything we assumed... was wrong...
Miss, you were with this lady earlier, right?
Oh, no... What should I do?
Maybe I'll kill you, too.
Why did you...?
I was abused by my parents.
My dad did perverted things to me,
and my jealous mom hit me.
Despite that, we pretended to be a happy family,
but it was a broken home.
That's why I killed them.
Do you think I'll be forgiven?
O-Of course no--
I was so surprised.
You two came just in time
to get in the way of my plans.
Did you really come from the future?
We...
Hey, if you really came from the future,
then will you tell me something?
What's the future me doing?
You are killed by your best friend.
Killed? By my best friend?
I don't have a best friend, though?
Hm?
Oh, I see, I see!
I get it now!
This is the future Estelle, right?
I knew it!
But why does Estelle kill me?
Because...
...you become a murderer...
I see. A murderer.
I see. That makes sense!
It makes sense?
I mean...
...killing people...
...is so much fun!
I won't forgive you.
You were still alive?
I should've stabbed you mor--
Selena...!
Ow! Ouch! That hurts!
You were tricking me the whole time?!
I thought we were friends!
Estelle's trying to kill me!
And when I become a murderer, Estelle will--
I thought we were friends!
I thought you could go
back to being a good girl!
The whole time! You were tricking me?!
Well?
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You...
...demon!
...murderer...
Estelle, please, wait.
Wait...
This... This...
This is...
Please come off...!
I don't need my memories of you.
I don't need any of them.
They can all disappear, along with you.
I shouldn't have saved you.
I shouldn't have thought
back on our time together.
I shouldn't have felt sorry about your death.
You should just die.
You should...
Goodbye, Selena.
Estelle?
Elaina, was it?
What did I...?
This is...?
You don't remember?
About Selena?
Who's that?
You sacrificed your
memories for magical power...
Who was that person to me...?
Don't worry about it. It doesn't matter anymore.
Oh? Okay...
I couldn't stop her...
She... with her own hands...
...killed her best friend twice...
I'm just an ordinary traveler.
Just an ordinary witch.
Inexperienced...
Unable to do anything...